嘿
Hey.
发生了什么
So what happened?
啊  我被抢劫了
Ah, I got robbed.
你还好吗
You okay?
还行  我是说  缝了几针  还有一根肋骨断了
Yeah. I mean, a couple stitches and a... broken rib.
我和凯特去了卡拉布里亚  把她安顿好
I went to Calabria's with Kate. Dropped her off.
给个晚安吻
Good night kiss.
准备度过这个夜晚  不过  呃  我最后出去喝了一杯
Was gonna spend the night, but, uh...I ended up going out for a drink after,
然后  然后在我回车上的时候
and-- and on my way back to my car,
一个家伙  不知道哪里跳出来的
some guy, outta nowhere, jumps me,
然后  在我清醒之前带着我的钱包就跑了
and-- and before I know it, just ran off with my wallet.
你有看清楚他吗
Did you get a look at him?
呃  没有  没有  那天  太  太晚了
Uh, no, no. It was... it was... it was late.
你去了哪家酒吧
What bar did you go to?
噢  我忘了  是一个在北边的酒吧
Oh, I don't know. Some bar on the North Side.
你知道  如果  如果你不介意  也许  呃
You know, if-- if you don't mind, maybe, uhm...
也许我可以自己告诉大家我发生了什么
maybe I'll tell people at work what happened myself.
我什么都不会说的
I won't say a word about anything.
谢了
Thanks.
法外真情
第三季  第十五集
翻译   章   鱼
校对  油 球
特效  转轮 枪
- 早  - 早上好
- Morning. - Good morning.
你好吗  谢谢
How are ya? Thank you.
啊  克肯达尔先生  很高兴再见到你
Ah, Mr. Kirkendall, nice to see you again.
嘿
Hey.
克肯达尔在等了
KirkendalI's waiting.
我知道  他来早了
I know. He's early.
噢  他总是很早
Oh, he's always early.
对  杰克还没来吗
Yeah. Is Jake here yet?
我不知道  他  呃  有一个
I don't know. He, uh... had a...
他  他可能会晚一点到
He... he might be running a little late.
为什么
Why?
- 嘿  - 早
- Hey. - Morning.
你是见鬼了吗
What the hell happened to you?
呃  昨晚小跑的时候
Uh... had a little... run-in last night.
有个家伙  呃  我  我  我正往车子那儿走  然后他  把我抢了
Some guy, uh... l-- l... I was walking to my car, and he... robbed me.
- 你没事吧  - 没有  我没事
- You all right? - Yeah. I'm fine.
呃  是不是  我们是不是应该开始了
Uh, shouldn't... shouldn't we be going?
啊  丹马克还不在
Ah, Denmar's not here yet.
丹马克还没来
Denmar's not coming.
什么
What?
克肯达尔想解雇他
Kirkendall wants to fire him.
他要解雇丹马克吗
He's firing Denmar?
对
Yeah.
他创立了公司
He founded the company.
对  他上个月还花了三千美元
Yeah, and he also spent about three grand
在某个绅士俱乐部招待了客户
at some gentlemen's club last month entertaining clients.
然后他主张那是商务支出
Then he submitted it as a business expense.
所以他打算为去了脱衣舞夜总会而解雇他吗
So he's gonna fire him for going to a strip club?
- 对  - 他想利用这个事情
- Yeah. - And he wants to use this as cause.
如果他可以
lf he can.
好吧  那
Okay, then.
杰克  让我  呃  和尼古拉斯聊一会
Jake, let me, uh, talk to Nicholas a minute.
好
Yeah.
- 听着  我  呃  想让杰克处理这件事  - 为什么
- Listen, l, uh, want Jake to handle this. - Why?
克肯达尔是个保守的人
Kirkendall, he's a conservative guy.
对  所以呢
Right. So?
好吧  他有着  和你一样的问题
Well, he's got problems... with your problems.
- 好吧  - 好
- Fine. - Yeah.
好
All right.
好了
Okay.
你确定你没事吗
You sure you're all right?
- 对  是的  - 好
- Yeah. Yeah. - Okay.
嘿  菲尼  你好吗
Hey, Finn. How ya doin'?
- 嘿  伯顿  - 你好
- Hey, Burton. - Good to see ya.
你记得杰克·斯特拉卡吧
You remember Jake Straka.
记得  记得  你没事吧  杰克
Sure. Sure. How ya been, Jake?
噢  没事  没事
Oh, good. Good.
- 你的眼睛怎么了
- What happened to your eye?
- 噢  - 抱歉打扰了
- Oh-- - I'm sorry to interrupt,
但是  呃  有个男的  说是刑警想找你谈谈
but, uh... there's a man... a detective who wants to talk to you.
好  我马上去
Right. I'll be right there.
呃  抱歉失陪一下
Uh... excuse me for a moment.
呃  我可没干什么违法的事  我向你保证
Uhm... I'm innocent of all charges, I assure you.
我相信  对
I'm sure. Yeah.
坐吧  菲尼
Sit down, Finn.
可怜的他昨晚被抢了
Poor guy got mugged last night.
不会吧  那太糟了
You're kidding. That's terrible.
尽管他是个硬朗的汉子  他会没事的
He's a tough kid, though. He'll be all right.
我只是想了解一些事情
I just want to follow up on a few things.
当然
Sure.
当我们在汽车旅馆谈论的时候
When we talked at the motel,
你说那个男人在你开门的时候把你推进了房间是吗
you said the man pushed you into the room while you were opening the door?
对
Right.
所以你没有和他一起
So you weren't with him.
没有
No.
他只是  呃  在停车场闲逛吗
He was just, uh... roaming around in the parking lot?
噢  我  我不知道
Oh... l... I have no idea.
你为什么会在汽车旅馆
Why were you at the motel?
- 什么意思  - 你住镇上  不是吗
- Excuse me? - You live in town, right?
所以我只是奇怪  为什么你要在途中停留在某个汽车旅馆
So I'm just wondering... why you would stay at some motel on Route 8.
好吧  我  我  你知道  我喝多了
Well, l... l... you know, I'd had a lot to drink,
呃  我不想开车回家  原因很明显
and, uh, I didn't want to drive home for... for obvious reasons,
所以我决定待在汽车旅馆
and so I decided to stay in a motel.
呃  医疗报告显示有些撕裂伤口和擦伤
Uh... medical report says that there were lacerations and abrasions
在你的腿部和腹股沟部
in your leg and groin area.
好的
Okay.
我只是想弄明白你的腿是怎么弄伤的  而且你知道
I'm just trying to understand how you got cuts on your legs and, you know...
如果是你被突然袭击了  这说不通啊
lf you got jumped, it doesn't add up.
嘿  你知道  那是场打斗
Hey, you know, it was a fight.
就是碰巧
Stuff happens.
- 对  - 对
- Right. - Right.
我知道有些事情谈论起来会难受
I know it's tough to talk about certain things.
我能理解
I understand that.
- 感谢您的配合  - 噢  我很乐意
- Thanks for your time. - Oh, my pleasure.
不好意思
Excuse me.
嘿  你怎么样
Hey, how ya doing?
不好不坏
Not bad.
打赌你做的双份拿铁一定比卢克好
Bet you a double latte you're doing better than Luke.
什么鬼
What's that?
他碰见了他妈妈和他最好的朋友
He walked in on his mother and his best friend.
他们在卧室里接吻  然后  卢克疯了
They were in the bedroom kissing, and... Luke went nuts.
拿起台灯痛打了他的朋友  还打了他的妈妈
Grabbed a lamp and beat up his friend. Hit his mother.
打坏了一些东西
Broke some stuff.
警察把他抓了起来  叫了我  然后我们就在这儿了
Cops picked him up... called me...and here we are.
他想干嘛
What does he want?
他想和他父亲生活在一起
He wants to live with his father.
但他不是华德·克里弗
But he's not exactly Ward Cleaver.
当他们在一起生活时  他曾经打了卢克的妈妈
He used to beat up Luke's mother when they were living together.
杰伊  他就像我最好的朋友
Jay? He's like my best friend.
曾经
Was.
警察撤销了对你的所有指控  卢克
Police have dropped the charges against you, Luke.
所以如果你想  你可以回家了
So if you want, you can go back to your home.
我告诉过那个女士  我想和我父亲一起生活
I told that lady I want to live with my father.
对  好吧  我们会先和你父亲谈谈
Right. Well, we'll have to speak to your father first.
他不是有史以来最伟大的人  但至少他是个男人
He's not the greatest person that's ever lived but... at least he's a guy.
苏珊娜会带你去一个收容所
Suzanne will take you to a shelter.
那是在我们能想出该怎么做之前你能待的地方
That's where you'll stay until we can figure out what to do.
有什么好解决的
What's there to figure out?
我妈就是个婊子
My mother's a whore.
噢  尼克
Oh, Nick.
你知道你不需要那么做的
You know you didn't have to do that.
什么
What?
那些花
The flowers.
什么花
Flowers?
对  噢  我以为那是你
Yeah. Oh. I thought that you...
逗你呢
I'm kidding.
你怎么知道我最喜欢百合花
How'd you know I liked lilies so much?
你去年告诉我的  说在你心情很糟的时候
Last year you told me that when you're in a bad mood,
你喜欢去农贸市场买白色的百合花
you like to go to the Farmer's Market and buy white lilies.
好吧  你能记得那件事真是贴心  谢谢你
Well, it was sweet of you to remember that. Thank you.
当然
Sure.
呃  我在想  呃  如果你今晚不是很忙的话
Uh... I was wondering, um...if you're not busy later tonight
如果你想吃个晚餐
if you want to get some dinner.
我很乐意
I'd like that.
好
Okay.
尼克·法林吗
Nick Fallin?
对
Yeah.
黛布拉·罗梅洛  我要和你谈谈我儿子卢克的事
Debra Romello. I was told that you have my son Luke.
好  我是他的律师
Well, I'm his lawyer.
我需要见他
I need to see him.
- 他在收容所  - 在哪儿
- He's at a shelter. - Where?
好吧  你需要打给社区服务中心去安排见面
Well, you'll need to call Social Services to arrange a visit.
但是警察已经撤销对他的指控了  不是吗
But the police have dropped the charges, right?
- 所以他可以回家了吗  - 是的  他只是不想回去
- So he can come home? - Yes he can. He just doesn't want to.
打给社区服务中心
Call Social Services.
你都没打电话
You don't even call.
你就
You just--
噢  我的天  小杰克
Oh, my God, Jakey.
对  没有很严重  真的
Yeah, it's not that bad, really.
发生什么了
What happened?
我被  一个  一个白痴  抢劫了昨晚
I got... Some... some idiot... robbed me last night.
打劫你吗
Robbed you?
对  但这不是什么大事  真的
Yeah. But it's no big deal, really.
噢  等下  老天  妈  我完全忘了买卖的事
Oh... wait. God, Ma. I totally forgot about the closing.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
没事  我们把它推迟到明天了
It's okay. We pushed it back to tomorrow.
买家们都很心烦  但是  我不相信有人
The buyer's all upset, but... I can't believe someone...
够了  好吗
Enough, okay?
- 我  - 抱歉  我没事  没事
- I'm-- - Sorry. I'm fine. I'm fine.
你看  妈  我晚点有个会议  好吗
Look, Ma, I'm late for a meeting, okay?
所以  呃  没什么事好担心的  真的
So, um, there's nothing to worry about. Really.
晚点我会打你电话谈  谈关于明天买卖的事
I'm gonna call you later about that... about that closing tomorrow.
好吗  谢了  妈
Okay? Thanks, Ma.
谢谢
Thank you.
你怎么预约到这儿的
How did you get a reservation here?
我  呃  跟D管家预约了
l, uh, talked to the Maitre d'.
呃  你知道  我为什么想吃晚餐的原因  呃
Uh, you know, the reason why I wanted to have dinner, um...
我们需要想想怎么解决
We need to figure out how this is going to work.
孩子的事
With the baby.
对  好吧  我  我猜
Right. Well, l-- I guess...
很大一部分情况  都取决于我们会怎样
a lot of that depends on what's going on with us.
呃
Uh...
我觉得我们需要制定  特点的条款
I think that we need to make... certain provisions.
比如呢
Like what?
好吧  有许多事情需要去考虑
Well, there's a lot of things to think about.
呃  呃  先从  钱开始
Um... uh, money... for starters.
抚养一个情况特殊的孩子是非常昂贵的
Raising a special needs child is very expensive.
我想建立一个信托基金
I would like to create a trust.
这样我就不用去担心了
Just so I don't have to worry about it.
好
Okay.
你同意吗
You agree?
如果  如果那是你想的话
lf... if that's what you want.
对  那
Yeah. That--
太好了
Great.
抱歉  我迟到了
Sorry I'm late.
那么  呃  我没有太多时间
So, uh, I don't have a lot of time.
- 那  - 请坐
- So... - Have a seat.
像我在电话里说的  我们抓住了这个家伙  汤姆·阿达斯
Like I said on the phone, we picked up this guy Tom Addas
在盛石用了你的信用卡
using your Visa card over at Lightstone's.
呃
Uh-huh.
在十分钟里买了大概价值两千美元的衣服
Bought about two thousand dollars' worth of clothes in ten minutes.
先让你看看能不能认出他
Just want to see if you recognize him.
有谁看着熟悉吗
Anyone look familiar?
没有
No.
一个都没有吗
No one?
我没看到他
I don't see him.
这个在右上角的家伙怎么样
How about the guy in the upper right here?
这个吗
This one?
不
No.
你知道  如果有那个混蛋对我做了他对你做的事
You know, if some punk did to me what he did to you...
那  我们可以结束了吗
So... are we done here?
可以
Yeah.
谢谢
Thanks.
儿童收容所
Children's Shelter.
嘿
Hey.
卢克
Luke.
嘿  你怎么样了  孩子
Hey, how ya doing, kid?
你长大了
You're gettin' big.
在打橄榄球吗
Playing football?
足球
Soccer.
噢
Oh.
好的
Great.
好吧  不管怎样  那  呃  我觉得你和我
Well, anyway, so, uh... I think this'll be good,
住在一起挺好的
me and you living together.
会很有趣
It'll be fun.
对
Yeah.
对  呃  你知道  你得换学校之类的
Yeah, um... You know, you're gonna have to change schools and stuff,
但是那没事
but that's okay.
对
Right.
而且我  我现在有女朋友了  卡莉
And I got... I got a girlfriend now. Carly.
你会喜欢她的
You'll like her.
她还是个好厨子
She's a good cook too.
你看  我不再喝酒了  所以事情都会变好的
Look I'm not drinking anymore... so things are gonna be better.
更加平静
A little more calm.
好的
Okay.
那你还有什么问题或者其他的吗
So you got any questions or anything?
呃  没有
Uh... no.
卢克
Luke.
你确定你想和你爸住在一起吗
Are you sure you want to live with your dad?
是的
Yeah.
好
Good.
那  呃  我猜这事过去不久后我会再见到你  呃
So, uh... I guess I'll see ya soon after all this, uh,
你知道  社区服务中心的手续已经完成了
you know, Social Services stuff is done.
皮特
Pete.
噢  我太想你了  宝贝
Oh, I've missed you so much, sweetie.
- 太想  太想了  - 放开我
- Mm, so, so much. - Get off me.
我不怪你乱发脾气  宝贝
I don't blame you for being upset, sweetheart.
我没有乱发脾气
I'm not upset.
对  你没有  没事的  如果你觉得那是真的发生了就发生了
Yes, you are, and it's okay if what you think happened really happened.
杰伊的父母在闹离婚
Jay's parents are getting a divorce.
所以呢
So?
那不容易
So it's not easy.
你经历过的
You went through it.
他  他当时很伤心
He... He was feeling sad.
他来找我
He came at me.
他吻了我  然后我不知道怎么处理  你就进来了
He kissed me... and l-- I didn't know how to react... and you walked in.
卢克  我原谅了你对我做的事
Luke, I forgive you for what you did to me.
我知道你不是真的想伤害我
I know you didn't mean to hurt me.
卢克
Luke.
嘿
Hey.
你为什么不告诉你的律师你想回家
Why don't you tell your lawyer you want to come home?
因为我不想回去
'Cause I don't want to.
一块鸡肉要21美元吗
$21 for a piece of chicken?
妈  就是这样的
Ma, it's all right.
里面甚至连蔬菜都没有  你还必须额外点
It doesn't even come with vegetables. You have to order that extra.
就是这样的  真的  你就点你想吃的
It's all right. Really. Just... just order what you want.
那  这个男的
So... this man.
不知道他是从哪儿冒出来的吗
He just came from outta nowhere?
呃  对  差不多是这样
Uh, yeah... pretty much.
我是说  我就是往车子那儿走然后
I mean, I just walking to my car and...
你看到他长什么样子了吗
Did you see what he looked like?
没有  不清楚
No. Not really.
我  我  呃  那天太晚了
l-- I was, uh... it was pretty late.
有多晚
How late?
很晚
Late.
呃  好了  这个  这个新餐厅叫  枫树花园
Uh... so listen, this new... this new place Maple Gardens...
听  听起来不错
l... it... sounds great.
我在网上看到过它家
I've been reading about it on the Internet.
呃  有很多活动
Uh... Iots of activities.
对  我知道  我很期待
Yeah, I know. I'm... I'm really excited.
新的开始
New beginnings.
我很高兴
I'm so glad.
那么  你想要  你想要什么
So... what do you... what do you want?
我想让那个狗娘养的在监狱待着
I want the son of a bitch to go to jail for a long time.
妈
Ma.
如果没人报警的话  谁知道之后可能会发生什么
lf someone hadn't called the police, who knows what might have happened?
谢谢
Thanks.
尼古拉斯  你看到杰克了吗
Nicholas, have you seen Jake?
没有
No.
他本来应该回来和我一起处理丹马克的调查
He was supposed to get back to me with that Denmar research.
好吧  我不想让你担心  我相信他会抽出时间来的
Well, I wouldn't let it worry you. I'm sure he's gonna get around to it.
好吧  抽时间可完成不了这事
Well, getting around to it is not gonna cut it.
我本来应该十分钟内就到克肯达尔那儿
I'm supposed to be over at KirkendalI's in ten minutes.
呃  那
Uh, well...
你知道  我可以帮你解决丹马克的案子
You know, I can help you out with this Denmar matter.
我没事
I'm okay.
我可以帮你做一点调查  如果你想的话
I could just do a little research for you, if you want.
不  我没事  我只是
No, I'm fine. I just...
我的胃因为那些止痛药有点难受  就是这样
my stomach's a little off because of these pain pills, that's all.
你有考虑过和谁谈谈吗  关于发生的事
Have you considered talking to someone... about what happened?
我  我没事  真的
I'm-- I'm fine. Really.
尼克  我说了我能搞定
Nick, I said I'd handle it.
我明天上午会留个备忘录在你桌上
I'll leave a memo on your desk tomorrow morning.
很抱歉打扰到您  斯特拉卡先生
Apologize for the inconvenience, Mr. Straka.
只是想向您更新下进展
Just wanted to update you.
听着  警探
Look, Detective.
我  我感谢您做的这些事
l... I appreciate what you're doing.
我  真的感谢
l-- I really do.
但是你知道  我  我现在非常的忙
But, you know, I am... I am very busy right now.
汽车旅馆的经理打了报警电话吗
The motel manager that dialed 91 1?
他从照片中认出了嫌疑犯
He picked the suspect out of the photo array.
好的
Uh-huh.
两秒钟就找到他了
Took him about two seconds.
我猜他看得很清楚
Guess he got a real good look at him.
好吧
Okay.
他的房间就在你的隔壁
His room is right next to the room you were in.
所有  想再试试吗
So... want to try again?
试什么
Try what?
看看照片
Looking at the photos.
我说了  我没看见他
Like I said, I didn't see him.
那么  如果让你到警局去怎么样
Well, how about if you come down to the station?
我们把这个家伙排在一个队伍里  之后也许你能认出他
We'll put the guy in a lineup. Maybe you'll see him then.
你知道  这是在浪费时间  我没有看见他
You know, it's a waste of time. I didn't see him.
我是说  这个叫阿达斯的家伙可能在CC餐厅为我煎过鸡蛋
I mean, this guy Addas could be serving me fried eggs at CC's Diner,
所以我不知道他是谁  你明白吗
and I wouldn't know who he is. You know?
你看  斯特拉卡先生
Look, Mr. Straka,
这个阿达斯  他是几起相似案件的嫌疑人
this Addas... he's been a suspect in a few similar cases.
所以你知道
So, you know,
如果我们能证明他不仅仅用了偷来的信用卡
if we could nail him on more than just using a stolen credit card,
那就太好了
it would be great.
我没看到他
I didn't see him.
噢  嘿  尼克
Oh, hey, Nick.
皮特·罗梅洛没有工作
Pete Romello's not gonna work.
什么
What?
- 他九个月前被捕了  - 我知道
- He got arrested nine months ago. - I know.
因为殴打他的女朋友
For beating up his girlfriend.
我打电话给他  告诉他卢克不能和他一起生活
I called him. Told him Luke can't live with him.
- 嗨  - 嘿
- Hi. - Hey.
- 昨晚过得很愉快  - 我也是
- I had a really nice time last night. - Me, too.
呃  我在信托中心搞金额的事儿  然后我想
Uh, I was fiddling around with some numbers for the trust, and I think that...
呃  如果你觉得太多了我想你可以告诉我  好吗
Uh, I want you to tell me if you think it's too much, okay?
但是我觉得  考虑到你赚了多少就放多少
But, I think that, given how much you make compared to how much...
- 多少  - 十万
- How much? - A hundred thousand.
- 如果你觉得太多了  - 好吧  我觉得可以放二十万
- If you think it's too much... - Well, I was thinking two hundred.
噢  真的吗
Oh. Really?
那  这是个特殊需要的基金  我们只能贡献一次
Well, since it's a Special Needs Trust, we can only contribute to it once.
我们可以算一算
We might as well make it count.
噢  对  好的
Oh. Right. Okay.
呃  我不确定我能出多少
Um, I'm not really sure how much I can...
- 我会处理的  - 嗯
- I'll take care of it. - Mm.
他妈的发生了什么
What the hell is going on?
呃  罗梅洛先生
Uh, Mr. Romello...
我刚接到电话告诉我说  卢克不能和我一起生活
I just got a call from some broad telling me that Luke can't live with me.
- 对  - 为什么
- Right. - Why?
是因为我  我在喝醉的时候揍了黛布拉几次吗
'Cause l-- I slapped that tramp Debra a couple times when I was drunk?
我是说  如果你看到她和你的兄弟鬼混的话
I mean, you'd smack her pretty face, too,
你也会揍她的漂亮脸蛋
if you walked in on her screwing your brother.
我想做这个决定更多的原因是
I think the decision has more to do with the fact
你在九个月前殴打了你的女朋友
that you assaulted your girlfriend nine months ago.
殴打吗  我是推了她
Assault? I pushed her.
卢克不能和你生活在一起  抱歉
Luke can't live with you. I'm sorry.
行  好  好
All right, fine. Fine.
把他送回到黛布拉那儿  是吗
Send him back to Deb, huh?
那对他来说会是好的
That'll be good for him.
斯特拉卡先生
Mr. Straka.
什么
What?
我们快要达成对阿达斯的认罪协议了
We're close to cutting a plea bargain with Addas.
噢  好的  对你来说不错
Oh. Well, good for you.
三对五
Three to five.
偏离性交
Deviate sexual intercourse.
这就是它的名字
That's what it's called.
好吧  事情不是这样的
Well, that's not what happened.
也许吧
Maybe.
那  阿达斯知道我没有认出他吗
Does... does Addas happen to know that I did not l.D. him?
判决几天之后才会正式生效
Deal won't be official for another few days,
所以如果你想改变主意的话  还有时间
so if you feel like changing your mind, there's time.
你知道  警探  我们  我们已经确认过这些事了  对吧
You know, Detective... we've-- we've kinda been through this, you know?
- 我知道  - 对
- I know. - Yeah.
但无论如何  真相都会大白的
But either way, the truth is gonna come out.
当有人认罪时
When somebody cops a plea,
他们必须告诉法官记录上发生了什么
they've gotta tell the judge what happened on the record.
所以不管怎么样  人们都会知道你们是怎么认识的
So no matter what... people are gonna know how you met.
你对他做了什么
What you did with him.
他对你做了什么
What he did to you.
如果你发现了这个人渣  让我们去审他
lf you l.D. this scumbag and let us go to trial...
我们会把他关十五年  否则
we'll put him away for fifteen years... otherwise...
呃  你叫杰伊是吗
Uh... your name Jay?
- 你是谁  - 卢卡·罗梅洛的律师
- Who are you? - Luke Romello's lawyer.
我  我只是想问你一些关于黛布拉的事
l-- I just wanted to ask you some questions about Debra.
比如什么
Like what?
你们在一起睡多久了
How long you been sleeping together?
听着  哥们  我们没睡  明白吗
Look, man, we don't. All right?
我是说  就因为那天卢克疯了
I mean, just because Luke went nuts that day
并不意味着发生了什么
doesn't mean anything's going on.
好吧  好  如果  如果你想
Okay. Well, if-- if you want,
我可以把你叫去证人席
I can have you called to the witness stand,
你可以在宣誓下  去法官面前解释
and you can explain in front of the judge, under oath,
你和你朋友的妈妈发生了什么
what you've been doing with your friend's mother.
你们在一起睡了多久
How long you been sleeping together?
你可以在这儿告诉我  或者你可以在法庭上告诉我  你自己决定
You can tell me here, or you can tell me in court. It's up to you.
好吧  我在这儿说
Fine, I'll do it here.
反正别让我上法庭之类的地方  好吗
Just don't call me into court or anything like that, okay?
我父母会杀了我
My parents will kill me.
好吧  那把真相告诉我
Well, then tell me the truth.
其实  没什么好说的
Well, there's not much to tell.
我是说  我们
I mean, we...
黛布拉和我有  你知道  做了那事  大概  三个月
Debra and I have been, you know, doing it for, like, three months.
- 你多大了  - 十六
- How old are you? - Sixteen.
她有在你十五岁的时候和你发生性关系吗
Did she ever have sex with you when you were fifteen?
不  她不会  如果你未成年
No. She won't... if you're underage.
你至少要十六岁
You gotta be at least sixteen.
这是她的规矩
It's like a rule with her.
好吧  所以我想你不是唯一一个与她有关系的人
All right, so I take it you're not the only person she's involved with.
不  还差得远呢  哥们
No. Not even close, man.
我是说  她是一个  有很多男孩子  你知道我什么意思吗
I mean, she's a... There's a lot of dudes, you know what I mean?
一个孩子告诉另一个孩子  然后就像一种小俱乐部
One kid tells another kid and then... It's kinda like this little club.
呃  卢克不能和他父亲生活在一起
Uh, Luke can't live with his father.
那太好了  所以我什么时候可以带他走
That's great. So when can I pick him up?
没那么容易
Not so easy.
什么意思
What do you mean?
好吧  卢克不想回家  他还是很生气
Well, Luke doesn't want to come home. He's still very angry.
但是  由于没有其他的选择
But, given the lack of alternatives,
呃  我感觉他如果可以改变他的想法
uh... I feel he'll probably change his mind.
那还有什么问题
So what's the problem?
好吧  问题就是你和其他青少年男孩发生性关系
Well, the problem is you like having sex with teenage boys.
什么
Excuse me?
让我们打开天窗说亮话  好吗
Let's just be up front about this, okay?
我不知道你在说什么  法林先生
I don't know what you're talking about, Mr. Fallin.
我试着给过你机会让你儿子回来
I'm trying to give you the chance to get your son back.
- 如果你同意进行心理咨询  - 心理咨询
- If you agree to get counseling... - Counseling?
对  进行心理咨询然后告诉卢克真相
Yes, get counseling and tell Luke the truth,
之后我会推荐他和你一起生活
then I will recommend that he live with you.
不  我不能告诉我儿子
No... I can't tell that to my son.
- 嗨  - 嘿
- Hi. - Hey.
我  呃  昨晚起草了一份信托协议  所以如果你有机会
l, uh, drafted a trust agreement last night, so whenever you get a chance...
- 好的  - 呃 - Okay. - And, uh,
唯一要讨论的就是谁将成为受托人
the only thing left really to discuss is who's going to be trustee.
然后我想  呃  如果你觉得没问题  我就去做
And I was thinking, uh... if it's okay with you, that I'd do it.
噢  我只是假设我们会是共同的受托人
Oh, I just assumed that we'd be co-trustees.
不  我  我宁愿这么做  我觉得会更容易些
No, l-- I'd rather do it this way. I think it'd be easier.
我想你完全投入进来  尼克
I want you to be involved, Nick.
相信我  我会做的
Believe me, I do.
我很感激你投入进来的钱
And I appreciate you putting up the money,
但是我觉得  如果我不用每次有什么我想做的事情都去找你
but I do think it would be better if I didn't have to track you down
得到你的同意  那样会更好
to get your consent every time I wanted to do something.
我没那么难找
I'm not so hard to find.
现在不难  但是  你知道  在一年或两年里  谁知道你会在哪儿
Not now, but, you know, in a year or two, who knows where you'll be?
我还是会在匹兹堡
I'll still be here in Pittsburgh.
好吧  呃  就还是考虑一下
Well, uh... just think about it.
好  当然
Okay, sure.
我们明天还继续  对吗
We're still on for tomorrow, right?
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
好的
All right.
呃  打扰一下
Uh... excuse me.
嗨  我是杰克·斯特拉卡
Hi. I'm Jake Straka.
好的
Okay.
我是那个  呃
I'm the guy who, um...
前几天晚上  在你打电话叫警察的时候
When you called the... called the police the other night on the...
我  我  我就是那个被打的人
l-- l-- I'm the guy who got beat up.
噢  是吗
Oh... yeah.
对  我  我  我就是想说  我  呃  我挺感谢你做的这些
Yeah, l-- l... I just wanted to say l, uh... I appreciate what you did.
没关系
No problem.
对  所以  呃  谢谢你
Yeah, so... um, Thank you.
噢
Oh.
对
Yeah.
对  那么  好吧  我  我和那个刑警聊了  呃  德马里亚
Yeah, so... well, l... I talked to the detective and, uh-- DeMaria,
他说你  就是那个人
and he said that you l.D# d the guy.
对  对  那  那很棒
Yeah. Yeah, that's... that's great.
但是你知道  同样的谈话  你知道
But, you know, by the same token, you know,
如果  不管什么理由  呃  你决定改变你的想法
if... for whatever reason, uh... you decided to change your mind
然后  呃  不参与  我是说  你懂的  我了解
and, uh... and not get involved, I mean, you know, I get it.
我是说  谁想找麻烦呢  对吧
I mean, who wants the hassle, right?
法院啊  还  还  还有律师啊  还有  还有  还有警察
Courts and... and-- and lawyers and... and-- and cops.
我是说  到结束那天  那个家伙还是会出来的  对吧
I mean, at the end of the day, the guy's probably gonna get off anyway, right?
那不是问题
Not a problem.
好吧  我  我只是想说我能理解
Well, l-- I'm just saying that I would understand.
听着
Look.
我知道这周围发生了什么  我不是傻子
I know what goes on around here. I'm not stupid.
所以当那个家伙把他的男朋友踢出去的时候
So when a guy starts kicking the hell outta his boyfriend
或者不管你叫他什么  我会划清界限
or whatever you call him... I gotta draw the line.
所以  说实话  我等不及要指正那个混蛋了
So, to be honest, I can't wait to testify against that punk.
格雷琴
Gretchen.
你有杰克的消息吗
Did you hear anything from Jake?
没有  我打了他家里的电话  他的手机  还发了邮件
No. I called his home phone, his cell phone... emailed him.
好吧  那  让我知道新消息  好吗  继续联系
All right. Well, let me know, okay? Keep trying.
- 嘿  儿子  - 嘿
- Hey, son. - Hey.
- 你怎么样  - 没事吧
- How ya doin'? - You all right?
没事  克肯达尔已经在会议室等了
Fine. KirkendalI's waiting in the conference room.
我们正试着把丹马克的问题解决
We're trying to finalize the Denmar matter
然而杰克  我  找不到他
and Jake just... l... can't find him.
好吧
Right.
我相信我们这边会更有利
I'm convinced we're in a better position.
呃  抱歉  呃  我很抱歉中断了谈话
Uh, excuse me. Um, I'm sorry for the interruption.
我刚才打了电话给杰克
I just got off the phone with Jake.
他有个私人问题需要他去处理
He has a personal matter he needs to attend to.
- 你  - 但是  我知道
- You... - But, I'm aware
您目前面临的问题  克肯达尔先生
of the issues you're facing, Mr. Kirkendall.
杰克昨天下午和我谈论过了
Jake talked about it yesterday afternoon.
重要的是在宾夕法尼亚没有什么决定性的案例
Bottom line is there's nothing directly on-point in Pennsylvania.
但是在俄亥俄州有个案例很完美
But there is an Ohio case that's perfect.
有一位CEO因为提交了在一个叫鲜肉宫殿的地方花费了
A CEO was fired for submitting a four hundred dollar expense report
四百美元的费用报告而被解雇了
from a place called the Flesh Palace.
它在宾夕法尼亚州的案件中被引用了三次
It's been cited three times in Pennsylvania cases,
所以它是条很好的法律
so it's pretty good law.
如果丹马克起诉了  你的防守会很稳固
lf Denmar sues, you have a solid defense.
- 所以我可以解雇他吗  - 是的
- So I can fire him? - Yes.
我可以发你一份所有问题概述的备忘录  如果你想要的话
I can send you a memo outlining all the issues, if you'd like.
好的  当然
Yeah, sure.
好吧  呃  谢了  尼古拉斯  很感谢你的帮助
Well, uh... thanks, Nicholas. I appreciate your help.
我的荣幸
My pleasure.
呃  我明白我没有加入你的团队  克肯达尔先生
Uh... I understand I'm not part of your team, Mr. Kirkendall,
但是我很高兴能帮您排忧解难
but I'm glad to be able to help you out.
当然
Sure.
如果在将来您有什么需要帮助的话  您知道在哪儿找我
And if you need any assistance in the future, you know where to find me.
呃
Hmm.
- 是谁  - 是我
- Who is it? - It's me.
妈
Ma.
我今天没什么事做  所以我给你做了这个
I had nothing to do today, so I made you this.
噢
Oh.
许多老照片和信  你知道
Lots of old pictures and letters and, you know,
都是你小时候的
stuff from your childhood.
谢谢
Thanks.
所以有什么关于那个攻击你的禽兽的消息了吗
So any word about that animal who attacked you?
没有
No.
- 没有吗  - 没有
- Nothing? - No.
好吧  新厨房很棒
Well, the new kitchen's great.
我很喜欢
I love it.
那个烤箱  它是个神奇的传送工具
The oven... It's one of those fancy convection things,
而且它花费  好像  大约  我不懂  不管你煮什么东西
and it takes, like, about, I don't know, twenty-five percent less time
都少花了二十五分钟因为它的这个风扇
to cook whatever you're cooking because it's got this fan...
你知道  妈  我  呃  我没有被抢劫
You know, Ma, l, um...I didn't just get mugged.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
事情比抢劫更糟
It was worse.
什么更糟
Worse?
那个家伙  他  呃  他做了一些事
That guy, he, uh... he did certain things.
什么事
Like what?
一些事
Certain things.
噢  杰克
Oh, Jake...
我  我没事  好吗
l-- I'm fine, okay?
我
l...
我只是需要告诉某人真相  就这样  有关发生的一切
I just need to tell someone the truth, that's all, about what happened.
你知道  最糟的是  在你知道之前
You know, the best part is that... before you know it,
整个城市就都会知道发生了什么  我发生的那些
the entire city's gonna know what happened. That I got...
人们就是喜欢悲剧  你知道吗
People just love a tragedy, you know?
试着表现出他们的心碎和同情心
Trying to be all heartbroken and sympathetic,
他们心底里就是喜欢这样
but deep down they just love it.
给他们一些谈资和笑料
Gives 'em something to talk about and laugh about.
杰克
Jake.
我不能让这家伙谈论发生的事
I cannot have this guy talking about what happened.
我就是不能
I just can't.
匹兹堡是个小地方  妈
Pittsburgh's a tiny place, Ma.
好了  进来吧
Yeah. Come on back.
抱歉过来打扰了
Sorry to just stop by.
没事  你想  你想喝一杯或者别的什么吗
That's all right. You want a... you want a drink or something?
噢  不  不  不  不了  谢谢
Oh, no, no, no. No, thanks.
我只是  呃  呃  我需要和你聊些事
I just, um... Um, I needed to talk to you about something.
当然  怎么了
Sure. What's up?
我  呃  我没有被抢劫
l, um... I didn't get mugged.
什么
What?
是一起性侵犯
It was a sexual assault.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
我在俱乐部遇见一个男人  一起喝了点酒
I met a guy at a club. Had a few drinks.
走回汽车旅馆
Went back to a motel.
事情就失去了控制
It got out of control.
那个  呃  警察捉到了那个家伙  然后他们试图操纵他
The, uh... police caught the guy, and they're trying to manipulate him
为越轨性交进行认罪协商
into a plea bargain for deviate sexual intercourse.
我的天
My God.
我的天  我
My God. l--
你怎么现在才告诉我
Why are you telling me this now?
我想把这事儿压住
I want to keep it quiet.
你能帮我吗
Can you help me?
噢
Oh...
我不知道
I don't know.
我不知道  杰克
I don't know, Jake.
我理解
I understand.
好
Okay.
谢谢你  伯顿
Thank you, Burton.
嘿  宝贝
Hey, sweetie. Mmm.
噢  抱歉  宝贝  我忍不住
Oh, I'm sorry, baby. I can't help it.
嗨
Hi.
差点忘了
Almost forgot.
你的卧室有了一个新电视
Got a new TV for your bedroom.
酷
Cool.
对  我朋友鲍比准备把DVD放进去
Yeah. My friend Bobby's gonna put the DVD in.
- 都准备好了  - 谢了
- Be ready to go. - Thanks.
呃  好了  宝贝
Uh... all right, sweetie.
我骗了你
I lied to you.
那天你回到家的时候
The other day when you came home...
你  呃
you were, uh...
当你  当你足球训练回来的时候
When-- when you went to soccer practice
你和你所有的朋友都很高兴
and you were having fun with all your friends...
然后杰伊停了下来
and Jay stopped by...
我们开始交谈
we started talking...
然后  我们  呃
and... then... we, uh...
他没有说一个字
He won't say a word.
没和任何人说
Not to anyone.
我也没有
And I won't.
这是我们的秘密
It will be our secret.
卢克
Luke.
每个人都会犯错
Everyone makes mistakes.
杰伊说他没告诉任何人是吗
Jay said he won't tell anyone?
对  对  他保证过
Yeah. Yeah, he promised.
怎么了
What?
我告诉了他真相  我照你说的做了
I told him the truth. I did what you asked.
我们有约定的
We had a deal.
她在说什么
What's she talking about?
不只是杰伊
It wasn't just Jay.
嘿
Hey.
呃  你可以做唯一的受托人  但是  呃  我需要你签一下这个
Uh, you can be sole trustee, but, uh, I'll need you to sign this.
一份保管同意书吗
A custody agreement?
对  我只是想确保宝宝出生后我能得到保护
Well, I just want to make sure that I'm protected after the baby's born.
尼克
Nick.
我想要法律和身体上的共同监护权  仅此而已
I want joint legal and physical custody, that's all.
这不是一笔交易  你知道  我不想用这个来谈判
This is not a deal, you know. I'm not negotiating this.
所以你只是想让我做你的银行  是这样吗
So you just want me to be your bank? That's it?
不  我只是想保证我能不依靠你
No. I just want to make sure that I can provide for our child
来保护我们的孩子  这非常简单
without having to depend on you. It's very simple.
简单吗  你觉得这简单吗
Simple? You think this is simple?
被告诉说不能信任我抚养自己的孩子吗
Being told that I can't be trusted to raise my own child?
等一下  我从没这么说
Wait a minute. I never said that.
好吧  你已经暗示过了
Well, you implied it.
不  我
No, I did--
好吧
All right.
那我想我们今晚不用一起吃饭了
So I assume we're not gonna have dinner tonight now.
为什么
Why?
好吧  我就是想如果你
Well, I just thought that if you...
露露  我们可以解决这个问题  好吗  我没有在担心
Lulu, we're gonna work through this, okay? I'm not worried.
我七点来接你
I'll pick you up at 7.
噢
Ohh.
你在这儿
Stay there.
我  呃  刚和地方检察官谈过
l, uh... just talked to the DA's office.
好
Okay.
他们  他们不想介入进来
They... they don't want to get involved.
好吧
Right.
很显然  他们确实想要这个狗娘养的
Apparently, they really want to get this son of a bitch,
不管有没有你的帮助
with your help or without.
好
Right.
抱歉
Sorry.
呃
Uh--
我  我就是很抱歉那个  呃  我把你牵扯进来
Yeah, I'm-- I'm just so sorry that, uh, I got you involved.
我  呃  我都不知道这是怎么发生的
l, uh... I don't really even know how this happened.
呃  但是  呃  所以我想说我觉得能和你工作很幸运  伯顿
Uhm... But, uh... So I say I feel very fortunate to work with you, Burton,
成为你的合伙人
to be your partner.
而且  我向你保证  我再也不会让我的原因使这家律师事务所
And... you have my word that I will never put myself in a position
有名声败坏的风险
to discredit this law firm ever again.
杰克  你是个好人  我很确信
Jake, you're a good man. I truly believe that.
但是你  你需要做出更好的决定
But you... you gotta make better decisions.
她很漂亮  不是吗
She's a pretty one, isn't she?
贝雷塔9000
Beretta 9000.
完美的自我防卫武器
Perfect weapon for self-defense.
它具有针对自然目标点的反射人体功能
It's got reflexive ergonomics for a natural point of aim.
3.6英寸的枪管
3.6 inch barrel.
合金制造  双重强制保险
Alloy finish. Ambidextrous safety levers.
多少钱
How much?
七百四十八
T48.
宾夕法尼亚的优待  没有等待期
Beauty part of Pennsylvania... no waiting period.
你想要那个小家伙  她是你的了
You want that puppy, she's yours.
我们需要谈谈
We need to talk.
好  怎么了
Okay. What?
你告诉地方检察官  事情已经结束了
You tell the DA the deaI's off.
你是无辜的  为什么要接受认罪协商
You're innocent. Why accept a plea bargain?
- 对  但是他们说  - 他们撒谎
- Yeah, but they said that... - They're lying.
没有我他们什么都得不到  我还什么都没说
Without me they got nothing, and I ain't talking.
对  没错  我什么都没说
Yeah, that's right. I'm not gonna say a word.
所以你去告诉你的律师说不行
So you tell your lawyer no deal.
不要问为什么  就说不行
Don't say why. Just say no deal.
明白了吗
Understand?
如果我发现  我因为你染病
And if I find out that I'm sick because of you...
我会杀了你
I will kill you.
你打算做什么
How're you doing?
你知道  我需要告诉法官你想去哪儿生活
You know, I need to tell the judge where you want to live.
我知道
I know.
好吧  所以如果你想你可以待在收容所
Okay. So you can stay in the shelter if you'd like,
或者我可以试着帮你找个寄养家庭
or I can try and find you a foster family.
那也许会花些时间  但是
It may take some time, but...
我只是想了很多我妈妈独自生活的事
I just think my mother's by herself too much.
当你一个人的时候事情很容易出事  你知道吗
Things happen when you're alone, you know?
如果我不在那儿了  事情只会变得更糟
lf I'm not there, it'll only make things worse.
我理解
I understand.
你觉得她还会这么做吗
Think she'll do it again?
可能
Probably.
我只是不想去什么随意的寄养家庭
I'm just not that into having some random foster family
让他们假装接受我  你知道吗
pretending to be into me... you know?
你想和你妈一起住吗
You want to live with your mom?
- 对  - 好吧
- Yeah. - All right.
那我就这么和法官说
That's what I'll tell the judge.
小杰克
Jakey.
妈
Ma?
你在这儿干嘛  很晚了
What're you doing here? It's late.
我睡不着
I couldn't sleep.
你知道  新的公寓  我不知道
You know, the new apartment... I don't know.
它  呃  所有东西都太他妈干净了
It's, uh... everything's so damn clean.
我是说
I mean...
你准备出去吗
Are you going out?
噢  小杰克  我真的很担心你
Ooh, Jakey, I'm really worried about you.
好吧  你什么意思
Well... what do you mean?
很多事你都不告诉我  比如你去哪儿了  去做什么
There are things that you don't tell me, like where you go and what you do.
那都无所谓  我知道这是你的生活
That's fine. I know it's your life and all,
但我是你妈妈  我会害怕
but I'm your mother and I'm scared.
听着  宝贝
Listen, honey...
你可以告诉我真相
you can tell me the truth.
你知道的  是吗
You know that, right?
我懂
I do.
妈
Ma.
没什么好说的
There's nothing to tell.
好吧  我今晚真的很高兴
Well, I had a really nice time.
我也是
Me, too.
呃
Uh...
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
对字幕有任何意见和建议的同学请加Q群：544487177
那  我  我想  明天见吧
So... l... I guess I'll see you tomorrow.
我知道你不信任我
I know you don't trust me.
我没怪你
I don't blame you.
但是我不想放弃
But I'm not giving up.
我是说  如果你想的话  你可以叫我去死 但是我不想放弃
I mean, you can tell me to go to hell if you want, but I'm not gonna give up.
早上好
Good morning.
- 嘿  - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
伯顿  那个  呃  我们讨论的问题
Burton, that, uh, problem we discussed.
对
Yeah.
已经被解决了
It's been resolved.
- 解决了吗  - 对
- Resolved? - Yeah.
就像从没发生过一样
So it's like it never happened.
好
Good.